Guide to the Joseph Strauss Bridge Plans, 1905-1935 M0163
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Joseph Strauss Bridge Plans
1905-1935
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Strauss, Joseph
M0163
96 tube(s) (circa 4,500 drawings)
Original bridge plans and construction drafts. Four different bridge types are represented: Strauss direct lift bridge, Strauss trunnion draw span, Strauss trunnion bascule bridge, and Strauss vertical lift bridge.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of original bridge plans and construction drafts. Four different bridge types are represented: Strauss direct lift bridge (S.D.L.B.), Strauss trunnion draw span (S.T.D.S.), Strauss trunnion bascule bridge (S.T.B.B.), and Strauss vertical lift bridge (S.V.L.B.). Years indicated after location of the project are the earliest and latest dated plans in the set; number in parentheses indicates number of plans or sketches in the set.
Provenance:
Transferred from the School of Engineering, Stanford University, 1966.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material is stored off-site and must be requested at least 96 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical / Historical
Joseph Baermann Strauss (1870-1938) was an American structural engineer who revolutionized the design of bascule bridges. He was the chief engineer of the Golden Gate Bridge.
Bridges; Civil engineering.; Blueprints.; Strauss, Joseph
- Thames River, New London, Connecticut, 1916 -1919; File 415: S.T.B.B.; (27). (Roll 1)
- Charles River, Boston, Massachusetts, 1911; File 417: S.T.B.B.; (10). (Roll 2)
- Marshfield, Massachusetts, for the New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad, 1910; File 425: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Roll 2)
- Trent Canal, Lindsay, Ontario, Canada, 1909 -1910; File 426: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 2)
- Trent Canal, Campbellford, Ontario, Canada, 1910; File 427: S.T.B.B.; (16). (Roll 3)
- Trent Canal, Grand Trunk Railway Bridge at Campbellford. Ontario, Canada, 1910; File 428: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 3)
- Saint Andrews Lock, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1911 -1912; File 429: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 3)
- Trent Canal, Campbellford, Ontario, Canada, 1911; File 431: S.T.B.B.; (1). (Roll 4)
- Second Narrows, Burrard Inlet, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1924; File 438: S.T.B.B.; (27). (Roll 4)
- Duwamish River - West Waterway, for the Northern Pacific Railway, 1909; File 439: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 4)
- Bridge 110, Newark Division, Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1910 -1911; File 450: S.T.B.B.; (11). (Roll 5)
- Ky-ax River, for the Grand Trunk Pacific Railway, 1910; File 457: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Roll 5)
- Buffalo River, for the Buffalo Creek Railroad Co., 1912; File 463: S.T.B.B.; (23). (Roll 5)
- Squam River, Gloucester, Massachusetts, 1910; File 468: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 6)
- Bronx Kills, for the New York Connecting Railroad, 1912; File 481: S.T.B.B.; (6). (Roll 6)
- Gatun River, for the Panama Railroad Co., File 484: S.T.B.B.; (11). (Roll 6)
- Black Rock Channel, Buffalo, New York, 1912; File 494: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 7)
- Sabine Neches Canal, Port Arthur, Texas, 1911 -1912; File 499: S.T.B.B.; (34). (Roll 7)
- Section 11, Erie Canal, Tonawanda, New York, 1917; File 501: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 8)
- Hoquiam River, Hoquiam, Washington, 1926; File 505: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 8)
- Princess Louise Docks, Quebec, Canada, 1910 -1911; File 507: S.T.B.B.; (13). (Roll 8)
- Chambly Canal, St. Johns, Quebec, Canada, 1915; File 513: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 9)
- Back River, Baltimore, Maryland, 1911; File 532: S.T.B.B.; (5). (Roll 9)
- Manchester, Massachusetts, 1911; File 534: S.T.B.B.; (10). (Roll 9)
- Lake Street Bridge, New Basin Canal, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1913; File 536: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 10)
- South Channel, Mystic River, Boston, Massachusetts, 1922; File 537: S.T.B.B.; (28). (Roll 10)
- St. Charles River, Quebec, Canada, 1911; File 538: S.T.B.B.; (24). (Roll 10)
- Portage River, Port Clinton, Ohio, 1911 -1912; File 542: S.T.B.B.; (25). (Roll 11)
- Assiniboine River, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1912; File 545: S.T.B.B.; (10). (Roll 11)
- Louisville and Portland Canal, 1913; File 555: S.T.B.B.; (13). (Roll 11)
- Saugus River, West Lynn, Massachusetts, 1911; File 557: S.T.B.B.; (2). (Roll 12)
- Salmon Bay Waterway for the Northern Pacific Railway, 1912; File 559: S.T.B.B.; (24). (Roll 12)
- Rainy Lake for the Canadian Northern Railway, 1912; File 561: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 12)
- San Pedro Inner Harbor; repairs, 1911-1929; File 562: S.T.B.B.; (23) and (2). (Roll 13)
- Calumet River, Chicago, Illinois, 1911; File 571: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 13)
- Cataraqui River, Kinston, Ontario, Canada, 1912 -1914; File 573: S.T.B.B.; (25). (Roll 13)
- Little Calumet River, 1924 -1925; File 578: S.T.B.B.; (18). (Roll 14)
- Ohio and Erie Canal, Massillon, Ohio, 1911 -1914; File 591: S.T.B.B.; (6). (Roll 14)
- Lachine Canal at Rockford, 1911; File 598: S.T.B.B.; (38). (Roll 15)
- Alterations to Lachine Canal at Rockford, 1923; File 598A:S.T.B.B.; (4). (Roll 15)
- Hagan Avenue Bridge, Old Basin Canal, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1911; File 603: S.T.B.B.; (6) (Roll 15)
- Buffalo Creek, Lake Shore & Michigan Southern Railway, 1911 -1912; File 607: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 16)
- Cohasset Narrows for the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Co., 1911; File 610: S.T.B.B.; (3). (Roll 16)
- Christiana River, Wilmington, Delaware, 1914 -1921; File 611: S.T.B.B.; (29). (Roll 16)
- South Branch, Chicago River, for St. Charles Air Line Railway, 1917; File 613: S.T.B.B.; (34). (Roll 17)
- Altamaha River for the Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1911 -1913; File 623: S.T.B.B.; (18). (Roll 17)
- Inside Thorofare at Albany Avenue, Atlantic City, New Jersey, File 624: S.T.B.B.; (19). (Roll 17)
- Calcasieu River, Calcasieu Parish, Louisiana, 1915; File 627: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 18)
- Passaic River, Bellville, New Jersey, 1913 -1914; File 634: S.T.B.B.; (40). (Roll 18)
- Arkansas River Bridge near Pine Bluff, Arkansas, 1913; File 635: S.D.L.B.; (31). (Roll 19)
- St. Charles River, Quebec, Canada, 1924; File 637: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 19)
- Main Street Bridge, East River, Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1914 -1916; File 649: S.T.B.B.; (25). (Roll 20)
- Mason Street Bridge, Fox River, Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1912 -1913; File 650: S.T.B.B.; (18). (Roll 20)
- Reconstruction of Mason Street Bridge, Fox River, Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1926; File 65OA:S.T.B.B.; (4). (Roll 20)
- Hackensack River at River Edge, Bergen County, New Jersey, 1912; File 653: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 21)
- South Saskatchewan River for the Canadian Pacific Railway, 1912; File 658: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 21)
- Corpus Christi Reef for the San Antonio & Arkansas Pass Railway, 1912; File 664: S.T.B.B.; (1). (Roll 21)
- River Rouge at Dix Road, Wayne County, Michigan, 1912; File 668: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 21)
- Assiniboine River, Winnipeg, Canada, 1912; File 670: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 22)
- Fraser River for the Grand Trunk Pacific Railway, 1913; File 676: S.T.B.B.; (16). (Roll 22)
- Wicomico River at Camden Avenue, Salisbury, Maryland, 1914; File 684: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 22)
- Buffalo Bayou, 1912; File 686: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 22)
- Mystic River for the Boston Elevated Railway, 1915; File 694: S.T.B.B.; (17). (Roll 23)
- South Street, Elizabeth, New Jersey, 1912; File 695: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 23)
- Broadway Bridge, Newton Creek, Camden, New Jersey, 1913; File 703: S.T.B.B.; (14). (Roll 23)
- Skansen, Trondheim, Norway, 1914; File 721: S.T.B.B.; (13). (Roll 24)
- Illinois River, for the Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Railroad, 1912 -1913; File 728: S.D.L.B.; (11). (Roll 24)
- Galena River, Galena, Illinois, 1913; File 732: S.T.B.B.; (17). (Roll 24)
- Sabine River, Orange, Texas, 1921; File 733: S.T.B.B.; (10). (Roll 25)
- East Chicago Canal for the B. & O. Railway, 1913; File 736: S.T.B.B.; (14). (Roll 25)
- Provencher Avenue, Red River, St. Boniface, Manitoba, Canada, 1913; File 750: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 25)
- D. & R. Canal, Trenton, New Jersey, File 751: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 25)
- Ebey Slough, Snohomish County, Washington, 1913; File 754: S.T.B.B.; (13). (Roll 26)
- Steilacoom Creek Waterway for the Northern Pacific Railway, 1913; File 755: S.D.L.B.; (14). (Roll 26)
- Johnson Street Bridge, Victoria Inner Harbor, Victoria, British Columbia, 1921; File 758: S.T.B.B.; (49). (Roll 27)
- Barnegat Bay, Island Heights, New Jersey, 1913; File 759: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 27)
- Wicomico River, Salisbury, Maryland, 1914; File 760: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 28)
- Islais Creek Channel, San Francisco, California, 1913 -1932; File 770: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 28)
- Wishkah River, Aberdeen, Washington, 1924; File 771: S.T.B.B.; (21). (Roll 28)
- Petaluma Creek, Petaluma, California, 1913; File 774: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 28)
- Aeroscope, for the Pacific Aeroscope Co., Panama- Pacific Exposition, San Francisco, California, 1914; File 780: S.T.B.B.; (2). (Roll 29)
- Stutson Street, Genesee River, Charlotte, New York, File 806: S.T.B.B.; (13). (Roll 29)
- Granite Avenue, Neponset River, File 809: S.T.B.B.; (10). (Roll 29)
- Sixth Street Bridge, Muskingum River, Muskingum Co., Ohio, File 810: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 29)
- Passaic River, Passaic, New Jersey, 1914; File 811: S.T.B.B.; (16). (Roll 30)
- Overpeck Creek, Leonia, New Jersey, 1913 -1914; File 814: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 30)
- M. & E. Canal, Posttown, Ohio, 1913; File 816: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 30)
- Ozama River, Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic, 1914; File 822: S.T.B.B.; (14). (Roll 31)
- Southern Yacht Club Channel, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1913; File 823: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 31)
- Sacramento River, Sacramento County, California, 1914 -1917; File 825: S.T.B.B.; (17). (Roll 31)
- Buffalo River, for the Delaware, Lackawanna & Western Railroad, 1914; File 828: S.T.B.B.; (39). (Roll 32)
- Pretoria Avenue Bridge, Rideau Canal, Ottawa, Canada, 1915; File 834: S.D.L.B.; (19). (Roll 32)
- Mystic River, for Boston Elevated Railway, 1915 -1916; File 840: S.T.B.B.; (18). (Roll 32)
- Almendares River, Havana, Cuba, 1916; File 844: S.T.B.B.; (28). (Roll 33)
- Inland Waterway from Norfolk, Virginia to Beaufort, North Carolina, 1914; File 846: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 33)
- Quinnipiac River at Forbes Avenue, New Haven, Connecticut, 1916; File 852: S.T.B.B.; (21). (Roll 33)
- Chelsea Creek, for the Boston & Albany Railroad Co., 1917 -1918; File 867: S.T.B.B.; (17). (Roll 33)
- Saugatuck River Channel, Westport, Connecticut, 1915; File 879: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 34)
- Sacramento River, Rio Vista, California, 1914 -1917; File 881: S.T.B.B.; (18). (Roll 34)
- College Creek, Annapolis, Maryland, 1914; File 891: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Roll 34)
- Corpus Christi Causeway, Nueces County, Texas, 1914 -1915; File 896: S.T.B.B.; (6). (Roll 35)
- Buffalo Bayou, Houston, Texas, 1914; File 897: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 35)
- Fourth Street Bridge, Channel Street Waterway, San Francisco, California, 1915; File 905: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 35)
- Northeast Cape Fear River, 1915; File 908: S.T.B.B.; (18). (Roll 35)
- East Branch of Elizabeth River, Norfolk, Virginia, 1916; File 912: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 36)
- City Park Avenue, New Basin Canal, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1915; File 916: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 36)
- United States Canal at 151st. Street, Lake County, Indiana, 1915; File 921: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 36)
- Matawan Creek, Monmouth County, New Jersey, 1915; File 928: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 36)
- New Basin Canal, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1915; File 931: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 37)
- The Estero Topila for the Tampico Panuco Valley Railway Co., Ltd.; Mexico, 1914 -1917; File 941: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 37)
- Richelieu River, Iberville, Quebec, Canada, 1915; File 944: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 37)
- Main Street Bridge, Merrimac River, Haverhill, Massachusetts, 1923; File 947: S.T.B.B.; (18). (Roll 37)
- Main Street, Fox River, Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1921 -1922; File 949: S.T.B.B.; (34). (Roll 38)
- Sidewalks on Main Street, beginning at the bridge in file 949, 1924; File 949A:S.T.B.B.; (3). (Roll 38)
- Inland Waterway, Cape May County, New Jersey, 1915; File 952: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 38)
- South River, Middlesex County, New Jersey, 1915; File 954: S.T.B.B.; (16). (Roll 38)
- Bickell's Bridge, St. Charles River, Quebec, Canada, 1925; File 955: S.T.B.B.; (1). (Roll 38)
- Wreck Lead Channel, Nassau County, New York, 1920 -1921; File 957: S.T.B.B.; (11). (Roll 38)
- Stratford Avenue Bridge, Pequonnock River, Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1916 -1917; File 979: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 39)
- Big Black River, Allen, Massachusetts, 1916; File 986: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 39)
- Shark River, Monmouth County, New Jersey, 1920; File 987: S.T.B.B.; (13). (Roll 39)
- Pequonnock River, Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1916; File 988: S.T.B.B.; (19). (Roll 39)
- East Washington Avenue Bridge, Pequonnock River, Bridgeport, Connecticut, File 989: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 40)
- Burlington Channel, Ontario, Canada, 1920; File 996: S.T.B.B.; (25). (Roll 40)
- South Front Street Bridge, Elizabeth River, Elizabeth New Jersey, 1920; File 1009: S.T.B.B.; (19). (Roll 40)
- Shippingsport Bridge, Illinois River, La Salle Township, Illinois, 1916; File 1015: S.D.L.B.; (13). (Roll 41)
- Barge Canal Crossing, Tonawanda, New York, 1917; File 1025: S.T.B.B.; (25). (Roll 41)
- Severn River, State Highway, Baltimore-Annapolis, Maryland, 1922; File 1033: S.T.B.B.; (10). (Roll 41)
- Mattawoman Creek, Indian Head, Maryland, 1917; File 1039: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 41)
- Griffith Street Bridge, Salem River, Salem, New Jersey, 1925; File 1043: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 42)
- Abbott Road Bridge, Buffalo River, Buffalo, New York, 1916 -1918; File 1050: S.T.B.B.; (21). (Roll 42)
- Rouge River, River Rouge, Michigan, 1918; File 1056: S.T.B.B.; (27) (Roll 42)
- Ocean City Road, Corsons Inlet, Cape May County, New Jersey, 1916; File 1062: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 43)
- Hylebos Waterway, Pierce County, Washington, 1924; File l064: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 43)
- Batiscan River, Montreal-Quebec Highway, 1920; File 1072: S.T.B.B.; (10). (Roll 43)
- Cuyahoga River, Cleveland, Ohio, 1917; File 1058: S.T.B.B.; (24). (Roll 43)
- Delaware and Raritan Canal, New Brunswick, New Jersey, 1917; File l088: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 44)
- Minnesota River, Hennepin and Dakota Counties, Minnesota, 1919; File 1089: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 44)
- Passaic River, Newark, New Jersey, 1920; File 1092: S.T.B.B.; (26). (Roll 44)
- Apalachicola River, Jackson and Gadsden Counties, Florida, 1918; File 1114: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 45)
- Industrial Canal, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1918; File 1115: S.T.B.B.; (27). (Roll 45)
- Industrial Canal, Port of New Orleans, Louisiana, at Southern Railway, Florida Walk, and L. &. N. R. R. Crossings, 1918; Files 1116, 1117, 1119: S.T.B.B.; (50). (Roll 46)
- Yamen Bridge, Pei Ho River, Tientsin, China, 1921; File 1122: S.T.B.B.; (36). (Roll 46)
- Proposed Gate, Ozark Dam, Joplin, Missouri, 1918; File 1123: S.T.B.B.; (2). (Roll 47)
- Welland River, Chippawa, Ontario, Canada, 1919; File 1128: S.T.B.B.; (15) (Roll 47)
- Broad Canal, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1922; File 1124: S.T.B.B.; (14). (Roll 47)
- Indiana Harbor Canal, Indiana Harbor, Indiana, 1919; File 1138: S.T.B.B.; (8). (Roll 47)
- Blackwater River, Milton, Florida, 1919 -1920; File 1142: S.T.B.B.; (10). (Roll 48)
- Piscataqua River, Portsmouth, New Hampshire - Kittery, Maine, 1920; File 1143: S.T.B.B.; (23). (Roll 48)
- New Bridge, Hackensack River, North Hackensack, New Jersey, 1922 -1927; File 1144: S.T.B.B.; (31). (Roll 48)
- Main Street Bridge, Kenosha Harbor, Kenosha, Wisconsin, 1919; File 1147: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 49)
- Rutland Railroad, Burlington, Vermont, 1919; File 1152: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 49)
- May Street, North River, St. Augustine, Florida, 1921; File 1174: S.T.B.B.; (16). (Roll 49)
- Hai Ho, Tientsin, China, 1924; File 1176: S.T.B.B.; (33). (Roll 50)
- Short Cut Canal, River Rouge District, Michigan, 1920; File 1178: S.T.B.B.; (2). (Roll 50)
- Bann River, Coleraine, Ireland, 1921; File 1181: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 50)
- Bayou Plaquemine, Plaquemine, Louisiana, 1920 -1921; File 1187: S.T.B.B.; (25). (Roll 50)
- Searchlight Investigation Section, Corps of Engineers, United States Army, 1920; File 1189: Strauss searchlight Apparatus 60" Type.; (14). (Roll 51)
- Mississippi River, for the Itasca County, Minnesota, 1920; File 1192: S.T.B.B.; (13). (Roll 51)
- Lynn River, Port Dover, Ontario, Canada, 1920; File 1193: S.T.B.B.; (11). (Roll 51)
- Navigation Lock, Wilson Dam, 1924; File 1205: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 51)
- State Street Bridge, Root River, Racine, Wisconsin, 1920; File 1200: S.T.B.B.; (32). (Roll 52)
- Ash Street Bridge, Neches River, Beaumont, Texas, 1922; File 1208: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 52)
- Inland Waterway at New Cut-off, Chesapeake & Delaware Canal, 1924; File 1215: S.T.B.B.; (23). (Roll 52)
- Cerritos Channel, Los Angeles, California, 1922; File 1220: S.T.B.B.; (42). (Roll 53)
- West Spokane Street, West Waterway, Seattle, Washington, 1922; File 1224: S.T.B.B.; (43). (Roll 53)
- Nacote Creek at Route 4, Atlantic County, New Jersey, 1922; File 1230: S.T.B.B.; (14). (Roll 54)
- Steamboat Slough, Sacramento County, California, 1922; File 1237: S.T.B.B.; (16). (Roll 54)
- Sacramento River, Freeport, California, 1927 -1928; File 1239: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 54)
- Troy Cohoes Bridge, Hudson River, 1921; File 1245: S.T.B.B.; (27). (Roll 54)
- Roskilde Fjord, Frederikssund, Denmark, 1923; File 1247: S.T.B.B.; (17). (Roll 55)
- Sadi-Carnot Bridge, Cette, France, 1922; File 1263: S.T.B.B.; (19). (Roll 55)
- Canal Of Cette, Cette, France, 1923; File 1264: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 55)
- Sacramento River, near Paintersville, California, 1922; File 1265: S.T.B.B.; (19). (Roll 56)
- New Rochelle to Glen Island, New York, 1921; File 1267: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 56)
- San Joaquin River, at Mossdale, California, 1924; File 1270: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 56)
- Tombigbee River between Marengo and Sumter Counties, Alabama, 1922; File 1271: S.D.L.B.; (24). (Roll 56)
- River Thames, Prairie Siding, Ontario, Canada, 1922 -1923; File 1272: S.T.B.B.; (16). (Roll 57)
- Mormon Channel, Stockton, California, 1925; File 1275 S.T.B.B.; (24) (Roll 57)
- Old Tampa Bay, Tampa-St. Petersburg Florida, 1923; File 1280 S.T.B.B.; (16). (Roll 57)
- Veranda Avenue Bridge, Presumpscott River, Cumberland County, Maine, 1921; File 1291: S.T.B.B.; (13). (Roll 58)
- St. John's River, Jacksonville, Florida, 1922 -1923; File 1295: S.T.B.B.; (33). (Roll 58)
- Platt Street, Hillsborough River, Tampa, Florida, 1924 -1925; File 1302: S.T.B.B.; (37). (Roll 58)
- Grassy Sound Channel, North Wildwood to Burleigh Road, Cape May County, New Jersey, 1922; File 1305: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 59)
- Canal Lock Chamber Number 4, Oregon City, Oregon, 1924; File 1320: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Roll 59)
- Rio Negro, Viedma & San Antonio, Argentina, 1922; File 1326: S.T.B.B.; (13). (Roll 59)
- Trail Creek, Michigan City, Indiana, 1922; File 1330: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 59)
- Grifton Bridge, Contentnea Creek, Lenoir and Pitt Counties, North Carolina, 1922; File 1332: S.T.B.B.; (14). (Roll 60)
- Lower Bank of the Mullica River, Atlantic and Burlington Counties, New Jersey, 1924; File 1333: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Roll 60)
- Sugimura Company, Ltd., Osaka, Japan, 1922; File 1338: S.D.L.B.; (8). (Roll 60)
- Spring Street, Ashley River, Charleston, South Carolina, 1923; File 1341: S.T.B.B.; (24). (Roll 60)
- New Dessouk Bridge, Egyptian States Railways, 1924; File 1350: S.T.B.B.; (24). (Roll 61)
- Bass River, Route 4, Burlington County, New Jersey, 1923; File 1363: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 61)
- Inland Waterway, Route 4, West Point Pleasant, New Jersey, 1923; File 1364: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 61)
- Manasquan River, Route 4, Ocean & Monmouth Counties, New Jersey, 1923; File 1365: S.T.B.B.; (10). (Roll 61)
- Sugimura Warehouse Company, Ltd., Osaka, Japan, 1923; File 1373: S.T.B.B.; (25). (Roll 62)
- Hillsborough River, Tampa, Florida, 1925; File 1375: S.T.B.B.; (32). (Roll 62)
- East Channel, Indian Creek, Miami Beach, Florida, 1924; File 1376: S.T.B.B.; (11). (Roll 62)
- Little Hoquiam River, Hoquiam, Washington, 1924; File 1381: S.T.B.B.; (9) (Roll 63)
- Congress Street, Fort Point Channel, Boston, Massachusetts, 1926 -1929; File 1382: S.T.B.B.; (20). (Roll 63)
- Welland Ship Canal, Port Robinson, Ontario, Canada, 1924; File 1388: S.T.B.B.; (18). (Roll 63)
- New Basin Canal, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1924; File 1392: S.T.B.B.; (34). (Roll 63)
- Louisville Avenue, Ouachita River, Monroe, Louisiana, 1928; File 1418: S.T.B.B.; (45). (Roll 64)
- Rio Teta Bridge, Cruce Rio Teta, 1924; File 1417:; (6). (Roll 64)
- Wood Bridge Creek, Perth Amboy, New Jersey, 1925; File 1400: S.T.B.B.; (21). (Roll 64)
- United States Canal, Menasha, Wisconsin, 1925; File 1425: S.T.B.B.; (26). (Roll 65)
- Buffalo River Bridge, No. 39247, 1925; File 1427: S.T.B.B.; (42). (Roll 65)
- Tuckahoe River, Route 14, Cape May and Atlantic Counties, New Jersey, 1925; File 1435: S.T.B.B.; (18). (Roll 66)
- Hillsborough River, Tampa, Florida, 1926; File 1434: S.T.B.B.; (49). (Roll 66)
- Mullica River, at Greenbank, Atlantic, and Burlington Counties, New Jersey, 1926; File 1447: S.T.D.S.; (7). (Roll 66)
- Napa River, near Vallejo, California, 1926; File 1463: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 67)
- Sonoma Creek, near Sears Point, California, 1926; File 1464: S.T.B.B.; (16). (Roll 67)
- Root River, Racine, Wisconsin, 1920; File 1465: S.T.B.B.; (34). (Roll 67)
- Cedars Creek and Clapboard Creek, File 1469-1470: S.T.B.B.; (4). (Roll 68)
- Bayshore Road, Sisters Creek, File 1471: S.T.B.B.; (4). (Roll 68)
- St. John's River, Green Cove Springs, Florida, 1926; File 1481: S.T.B.B.; (21). (Roll 68)
- Chicago River, 1928; File 1485: S.T.B.B.; (26). (Roll 68)
- Illinois River at Florence, Illinois, 1926; File 1487: S.T.L.B.; (27). (Roll 69)
- West Twin River, Two Rivers, Wisconsin, 1926 -1927; File 1488: S.T.B.B.; (25). (Roll 69)
- South Branch of Chicago River, 1927; File 1490: S.T.B.B.; (32). (Roll 69)
- St. Charles River, Quebec, Canada, 1930; File 1493: S.T.B.B.; (24). (Roll 70)
- 79th. Street Causeway, Biscayne Bay, Miami, Florida, 1927; File 1503: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 70)
- Illinois River, Pekin, Illinois, 1927; File 1507: S.V.L.B.; (16). (Roll 70)
- Matanzas River, Crescent Beach, Florida, 1927; File 1525: S.T.B.B.; (9). (Roll 70)
- Beasleys Point and Somers Point, New Jersey, 1927; File 1533: S.T.B.B.; (14). (Roll 71)
- Government Canal, Little Chute, Wisconsin, 1927; File 1535: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 71)
- Wading River, Wading, New Jersey, 1928; File 1556: S.T.B.B.; (7). (Roll 71)
- City Park Avenue Bridge over Swan Creek, Toledo, Ohio, 1928; File 1567: S.T.B.B.; (12). (Roll 71)
- Inside Thorofare, Dorset Blvd., Ventnor, New Jersey, 1929; File 1574: S.T.B.B.; (31). (Roll 72)
- Burlington Channel, Ontario, Canada, 1930; File 1581: S.T.B.B.; (29). (Roll 72)
- Illinois River, La Salle, Illinois, 1928; File 1568: S.V.L.B.; (14). (Roll 72)
- Wanamaker Avenue, Darby Creek, Delaware County, Pennsylvania, 1929; File 1591: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 73)
- Beach Thorofare, Venice Park, New Jersey, 1929; File 1598: S.T.B.B.; (17). (Roll 73)
- Wappinger Creek, New Hamburg, New York, 1929; File 1605: S.T.B.B.; (21). (Roll 73)
- West Waterway, Duwamish River. Seattle, Washington, 1931; File 1611: S.T.B.B.; (15). (Roll 74)
- Illinois River, Hardin, Illinois, 1930; File 1617: S.V.L.B.; (17). (Roll 74)
- Green River, Rockport, Kentucky, 1930 -1931; File 1626: S.T.B.B.; (25). (Roll 74)
- Chicago Sanitary Canal, Justice, Illinois, 1931; File 1640: S.V.L.B.; (23). (filed with Bundle #65). (Roll 75)
- Longview Bridge, Columbia River, Longview, Washington, 1928 -1929; File unident.; (97). (Roll 76)
- Independence Bridge, Independence, Missouri, 1926 -1928; File 1528: S.T.B.B.; (16). (Roll 77)
- Quincy Memorial Bridge, Mississippi River, 1928; File 1555: S.T.B.B.; (23). (Roll 77)
- Cedar Street Bridge, Illinois River, Peoria, Illinois, 1929; File 1565:; (47). (Roll 78)
- Ship Channel, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1929; File 1580: S.T.B.B.; (22). (Roll 78)